Okay. Now that we've gone over the history of
好了 我们已经回顾了 A/B 测试的历史
AB testing, let's start diving into our example.
现在让我们来看一些示例
Throughout this course,
在整个课程中
we'll use an example of an online education company sort of like Udacity.
我们会使用与优达学城相似的一个在线教育公司作为示例
Let's just call it Audacity.
我们称它为 Audacity
Audacity is focused specifically on finance courses, and
Audacity 专攻金融课程
they're trying to test features that increase student engagement.
他们在试着测试功能 增强学生互动
First, let's talk about what a typical user flow
首先 让我们来谈谈 Audacity 网站
through the Audacity site might look like.
典型的用户流程是怎样的
You would probably see that the largest number of users visit the homepage.
你可以看到主页的最大用户访问数
Then a subset of those users might explore the site by looking at a few
其中有一些用户会查看一些不同页面
different pages.
探索网站
An even smaller group might create an account.
还有更少数的人会创建账户
And the final group might reach some sort of completion.
最后有一些人会以某种方式完成探索
Maybe they make a purchase, complete a class, finish a series of classes, or
比如说购买、上课、完成一系列课程
share the site on their blog, for example.
或者在博客分享网站 等等
This type of flow is often called the customer funnel, and
这种流程类型通常被称为客户漏斗模型
it's a common idea for websites.
对网站而言 这是个很常见的概念
The idea is that you have the largest number of events at
在这个概念中 漏斗最上层的是最经常发生的事件
the top of your funnel, and as you go down, it becomes rarer and
越往下走 客户走到那一步的几率
rarer that someone would reach that level.
就越来越小
The idea is that users are trickling down the funnel, but
客户沿着漏斗从上到下渗透
that's kind of a simplistic idea.
但这个概念太过简单化了
Customers don't actually enter, create an account, and
客户不会总是沿袭进入、创建账户
then complete a class in a consistent manner.
完成课程这样的顺序
There's a lot of back and forth swirl between the different states, and
客户会在不同的状态间来回涡旋
repeat visitors who skip over intermediate steps.
而回访者会跳过中间这些步骤
We'll be discussing the funnel and swirl more and
我们会在第三课中进一步讨论漏斗和涡旋
how it ties to metric choice in lesson three.
及其与指标选择的关系
For the rest of lesson one, we're going to go over a simple experiment from
而在后面的第一课内容中 我们会从头到尾讲解一个简单的实验
start to finish, so that you can see all the steps that are necessary for
让你了解实验从头到尾
running an experiment end to end.
需要采取哪些步骤
In future lessons,
在以后的课程中
we'll be going through several of the steps in more detail.
我们会更具体地讨论其中几个步骤
We'll consider an experimental change to Audacity's homepage.
我们考虑对 Audacity 主页进行实验性地变更
Specifically, we'll consider a change to the Start Now button.
具体来说 我们考虑改变一下 现在开始 这个按钮
If users click this button, they can see a list of Audacity's courses.
如果用户点击这个按钮 他们会看到 Audacity 的课程清单
In this experiment, we'll make a simple change,
在这次实验中 我们会进行一个简单的变更
making the Start Now button pink instead of orange.
把 现在开始 这个按钮从橙色改为粉色
So a first pass hypothesis for
我们这个简单的实验的第一个假设就是
our simple experiment is that changing the Start Now button from orange to pink
把 现在开始 这个键从橙色改为粉色
will increase how many students explore Audacity's courses?
会增加多少探索 Audacity 课程的学生
That is, move on to the second step of the funnel.
也就是 移动至漏斗的第二步